<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?><Search><pages Count="32"><page Index="1" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[TECHNOLOGY VISIONDigital Integration Digital Platform Digital Workplace Predictive EnterpriseSHAPING YOUR DIGITAL BUSINESS]]></page><page Index="2" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[TECHNOLOGY VISIONBrochure Design   More and more, our interactions are in the digita bank to do your banking? Sat with a travel agorder takeout?In the last minute, Amazon generated $83,000 in online sales. Google received more than 4M search queries. And Yelp users posted more than 26,000 reviews.Our lives in the business world are closely mir- roring our consumer interactions. Digital busi- ness is here to stay, from how we interact with our customers to how we team with our internal colleagues. Much of our business has moved to digital and virtual realms.The result of this move is a melting pot out of which entirely new business models are born. Current thinking will not get any of us to a suc- cessful future.Par for the course is confusion, disruption and waves of change—all of which can be trying for any organization.2]]></page><page Index="3" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[  Brochure Designal realm. When was the last time you visited ent to book tickets? Made a phone call to CONTENTS06 DIGITAL INTEGRATION 12 DIGITAL PLATFORM18 DIGITAL WORKPLACE24 PREDICTIVE ENTERPRISETECHNOLOGY VISION AUTHORS & CONTRIBUTORS313]]></page><page Index="4" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[TECHNOLOGY VISIONBrochure Design   The savvy will  nd the sweet spot inherent in any radical shift.WHY DIGITAL? WHY NOW?Computing is cheap, thanks to the cloud. Technol- ogy is now so inexpensive and disposable, it is em- bedded in everything—from shoes to jewelry, man- ufacturing machines to mobile phones.Computing is also radically more consumable than in the recent past. From website creation to basic analytics, we are in a DIY, self-service model.And last, computing is now ubiquitous. With the rise of the IoT and mobile devices, we are living and working within a digital fabric that is everywhere around us.Despite this fabric, roughly 70 percent of business- es have yet to begin their digital transformation. Yet, 87 percent of companies think that digital transformation will provide a competitive advan- tage. And they are right. Companies that are suc- cessful in making the digital transformation are, on average, 26% more pro table than competitors.Which leaves us with work to do.OPERATING MODELS MUST SHIFT TO FUTURE FOCUSThe way that companies operate must shift. One poor customer review spreads via social media like wild re. Companies like Tesla update their prod- ucts overnight. The speed at which businesses un- derstand and react to changing business circum- stances has to radically improve. And that means the management models that they had in place for decades are going to have to transform at the same time.4]]></page><page Index="5" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[  Brochure DesignHUMAN CAPITAL MATTERS MORE THAN EVERNothing happens without talent, right? Not even the best technology in the world can succeed with- out the bene t of the talented minds that put it to use.Businesses are not run by systems. In the digital world, the capabilities of our people are going to be leveraged like never before. We have to focus on how talent interacts, shares information, and gen- erally drives their own impact inside of our com- panies.YOUR ORGANIZATION:AT THE POINT OF IMPACTAt this point, most businesses have a choice to make: to be the observer of the changing business world or to help shape their place in it. Change will come either way.For those who want to take the rudder, we see four areas of digital business that are key to shaping your company’s future:Digital Integration Digital PlatformDigital Workplace Predictive Enterprise5]]></page><page Index="6" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[TECHNOLOGY VISIONBrochure Design   DIGITAL INTEGRATION6]]></page><page Index="7" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[  Brochure DesignTHE CONNECTIVE FABRIC OF A DIGITAL WORLDAs CIOs and CTOsare thrust into the innovation driver’s seat, the systems they work with must re ect the pace and constant changing demands of the digital reality.Digital business transformation demands integration more com- plex than anything we have seen historically. In the future, compa- nies will better serve customers because they are stitched into the fabric of their customers’ lives— from ideation to supply chain to delivery, more targeted outcomes will be possible.The rise of platform-based eco- systems means any organization now needs a digital underpinning that goes beyond its virtual walls to include partners of all types— partners who change more fre- quently than ever. Over the next several years, many in IT leader- ship will turn to an intelligent inte- gration layer to address the issue.7“Right now, companies are rebuilding their technical foundations due to the tectonic shift of digitization. We expect this to continue at rapid pace for the next several years.”—David Barrett, Director of Technology, Digital Integration, Neudesic]]></page><page Index="8" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[TECHNOLOGY VISIONBrochure Design   Hard wiring is going the way of the dinosaur. Infrastructures are now less tangible, instead being built on an agile software model, from APIs and cloud to microservices and bimodal IT. Citizen integrators are on the rise in most organizations. They are the heralds of change in a new digitally connected world.By 2022, IoT will save consumers and businesses $1 trillion a year in maintenance, services and consumables.(Source: “Top Strategic Predictions for 2017 and Beyond: Surviving the Storm Winds of Digital Disruption,” Gartner, October 14, 2016)Organizations need agile, scalable integration approaches that can be choreographed in real time, multiple times in a day, an hour, sometimes even a minute. The concept of “composable” in- frastructure leverages best of breed platforms and technologies to form an optimized solution. The ability to compose infrastructure on the fly is the ultimate agility in a digital world.Enter the digital integration platform. This intel- ligent network provides a unifying connectivity among people, applications and devices in dif- ferent locations or business units—this connec- tivity is the intelligent integration layer. It cre- ates the borderless enterprise, which includes your company, your partners, your customers, and the physical world. It is adaptive—a living, breathing organism versus the staid, fixed behe- moths of old.8]]></page><page Index="9" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[  Brochure DesignIOT AND MOBILITY TAX TRADITIONAL SYSTEMS WHILE CITIZEN INTEGRATION SAVES THE DAYThe rise of smart “things” in the physical world, along with the rise of business platforms into ecosystems, creates vast volumes of data enter- ing the org., being exchanged and transformed into fuel for business results. To realize the full benefits of this scenario, the organization’s in- telligent integration layer must support this sce- nario. Many organizations are turning to cloud- based computing at the edge as a basic tool just to keep pace.Customers, employees, and partners expect access to information anywhere on any device. Increasingly, business groups have larger budg- ets for technical initiatives and lead the way in technical solutions, relegating tradition-central- ized IT to a secondary role or none at all. Basic integration platforms now exist across disparate business or partner systems, creating a break from the monolithic integration approach of the past.As the citizen integrator concept grows—out of sheer business necessity—and as digitization progresses, integration will become less expen- sive over time.In the near future, we see some IT departments mastering the new approach to agile business, providing the tools, oversight and flexible pro- cesses to enable the business to achieve its goals without the central integration insisted upon in the past. The digital integration platform of the future requires centralized oversight versus centralized control. Adobe has done just this by gradually implementing a DIY integration strat- egy. Within the first 10 months, roughly 400 ad hoc and citizen integrators were enabled to use the company’s Hybrid Integration Platform. The result? More than 600 integration interfaces and 200+ APIs, which would have taken a centralized integration competency center years to com- plete.Citizen integration could save the day, if central IT can get governance frameworks right. Gartner assumes that by 2018, at least 50 percent of new integration flows will be implemented by citizen integrators. With the maelstrom of integrations that go on each day in large corporations, gov- ernance becomes an immediate priority. Em- ployees, or “citizen integrators” are empowered to “code” various pieces of infrastructure, as it relates to their goals for the customer or busi- ness. DIY integration, backed by a strong central framework, is the path forward. And that change will bring interoperability to the fore.(Source: ”Gartner CIO Call to Action- Shake Up Your Integration Strategy to Enable Digital Transformation”, Gartner, November 26, 2015)9]]></page><page Index="10" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[TECHNOLOGY VISIONINTEGRATION ORINTEROPERABILITY?Both, for the near future. Integration enables interoperability. The simple difference is that integration makes independently-designed IT elements work together while interoperabili- ty, according to Gartner, focuses more on no outstanding work remaining to get devices or software to talk to each other after they are in- tegrated. Interoperability is the goal, but most companies are a long way from it.Brochure DesignBy 2020, over 20 billion connected things will be in use worldwide.(Source: “Gartner Says 6.4 Billion Connected” Gartner, November 10, 2015)A SYSTEM THAT THINKS LIKE ITS HUMAN CREATORSAs analytics and artificial intelligence mature, the event-driven architecture will feed informa- tion into emerging cognitive and neuromorphic computing models. These models generate ac- tionable intelligence that humans alone cannot predict. We see the irony of modeling machine intelligence after the human brain it seeks to replace, due to the limitations of the human brain.10fffff]]></page><page Index="11" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[Brochure Design40% of IoT early movers believe that data integration (24%) or analysis (16%) will be the biggest technology hurdles to clear.(Source: “The Intersection of IoT and Big Data” Enterprise Strategy Group, March 28, 2016)11EVENT-DRIVEN ARCHITECTURE IN A DIGITAL INTEGRATION PLATFORM WILL CHANGE INDUSTRIES AS WE KNOW THEMSmart carts help customers navigate the store and see real-time shopping cart costsCustomers scan product barcodes to access product information and see reviewsImproved inventory increases product availability in storeCustomers request help via mobile devices and kiosks in-storesPersonalized digital coupons served to customers via mobile and wearablesSmart carts help customers navigate the store and see real-time shopping cart costsSigns display content in real time, customized to speciic stores and locationsCustomers check-out automatically via scan full cart contentsStores monitor visitors and purchase histories to provide higher level serviceStores monitor customer traic patterns to help efectively position related productsStores can change prices in real time based on demand or other factorsStores reduce labor and reallocate register space to display productsSmart ShoppingSmart SelectionSmart CartsSmart ShelvesSmart Price TagsSmart ServiceSmart CheckoutDESIGNING FOR OUTCOMES REQUIRES A FLEXIBLE DIGITAL INTEGRATIONDesigning successful experiences, whether for employees, customers or platform partners, starts with design thinking. Design thinking, at its base, is an iterative approach to problem solving that involves rapid experimentation and prototyping. As users test the product or service, changes are made in almost real time.To get design thinking right in a digital enter- prise, an agile technology foundation with an in- telligent integration layer—is a given.MICROSERVICES FOR DISTRIBUTED ARCHITECTUREMicroservices-based software will continue to evolve rapidly over the next several years. It replaces clunky and inflexible monolithic archi- tectures with composable focused platforms to provide rapid cycle times, selective scaling and right-sized technology choice. Today, most cloud-native applications are built using scala- ble, distributed architectures based on micros- ervices.Stores can ofer related items to upsell and cross-sellSmart shelves detect inventory to trigger replenishment or reorder when low, increasing salesStores provide better on-demand service to increase sales]]></page><page Index="12" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[TECHNOLOGY VISIONBrochure Design   DIGITAL PLATFORM12]]></page><page Index="13" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[  Brochure DesignDIGITAL AS A SPRINGBOARD TO TRANSFORMATIVE INNOVATIONDi erentiation through innovation is becoming less art, more science.The presence of one key under- pinning—a digital platform—en- ables innovation. The absence of that underpinning is an Achilles heel no modern organization can survive.Innovating effectively and deliv- ering new digital experiences—a continuous cycle of delivering the new—is necessary for market rel- evance in an age where software is outdated within months.48%48% of global businesses don’t know what their industry will look like in three years.(Source: Vanson Bourne Study for Dell Technologies, ”Digital Future Executive Summary”, Dell Technologies, 2016)1375%According to The Economist, “75% of CEOs want their CIOs to play an advisory business strategy role—not just an IT viewpoint—in the C-SUITE (sic).”]]></page><page Index="14" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[TECHNOLOGY VISIONBrochure Design   Critical to any company’s success is the speed with which teams can recognize opportunity and turn those opportunities into transformative digital implementations, products and services. Speed, tempered with security and governance, is well worth the challenge of balancing these sometimes opposing forces.When competitive advantage hinges on tailored solutions with a short shelf life, the system that supports those solutions must allow for constant change. In an era where Tesla cars can be made safer overnight via a simple software upgrade, all businesses need to offer similar ease and flexibility to their customers. Whether altering internal process flows to cut costs, offering cus- tomers desired upgrades to products, or accom- modating a supplier’s changed delivery sched- ule, organizations need system speed and ease to match the pace of business.Most organizations spend roughly 80 percent of their IT investments on optimization of existing systems, which leaves only a small fraction of existing budget for investing in new ideas and business opportunities through technology. In addition, 60 to 90 percent of features in any giv- en project backlog currently produce little to no value. There is room for increased wisdom on how to divvy up the corporate spend.Organizations must maximize the investments made in transformative business initiatives by optimizing how they develop and deliver tech- nology solutions—through a robust digital plat- form.Think of a digital platform less as a thing, and more as a way of doing business to unlock value from all corners of your enterprise.14(Source: Jez Humble, Joanne Molesky, Barry O’Reilly. “Lean Enterprise: How High Performance Organizations Innovate at Scale” O’Reilly Media, 2014)]]></page><page Index="15" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[  Brochure DesignPORTRAIT OF A DIGITAL LEADERREVENUE CHANGE OVER THE LAST TWO YEARSPercentage saying how their revenue changed in the past two years.IT’S MOST IMPORTANT CONTRIBUTIONS FOR THE NEXT THREE YEARSPercentage who see each of the following as the most important contribution over the next three years.48% - Drive business innovation through IT47% - Manage security and risk47% - Establish architectures to support digital41% - Support business-led IT initiatives28% - Provide access to tech capabilities (vendor)21% - Lead and implement most IT projects(Source: “Driving Digital Transformation: New Skills For Leaders, New Role For The CIO” Harvard Business Review, 2015)15]]></page><page Index="16" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[TECHNOLOGY VISIONBrochure Design   CHANGING YOUR INNOVATION PIPELINEA potent digital platform addresses far more than just technology. Currently, most companies spend about 83 percent of their IT budget on maintenance and optimization of existing systems. That leaves a scant 17 percent to invest in innovation to move the business toward true growth. A digital platform helps ensure a better coor- dinated and orchestrated spend.FOUR MAIN ELEMENTS ARE KEY FOR SUCCESS AND TRUE INNOVATION:ProcessArchitectureTechnologyInfrastructure13Process 2Innovation is a habit and your processes must enable faster feedback cycles and create a culture for learning. Neudesic helps you deliver value with both speed and safety.Technology 4Choosing the correct technology is imperative for innovation. We look for languages and platforms that have high productivity and maximal impact. And we make a few products for added e ect!ArchitectureInnovation with a digital platform means that the architecture is agile for change and resilient to failure. We have a long history of designing large systems that can still ‘turn on a dime’.InfrastructureThe foundation for innovative platforms is a robust infrastructure. Just like a castle cannot rest on sand, your digital platform cannot rely on archaic hardware provisioning models.16</>$$$$</>]]></page><page Index="17" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[  Brochure DesignCIO DIGITAL RESPONSIBILITIESStrategyAgility/Bimodal IT Architecture Talent GovernanceCulturehttp://www.gartner.com/smarterwithgartner/six-cio-responsibilities-for-digital-business-leadership/Digital Business LeaderDigital EngineIT Leadership60%60% of businesses are unable to meet customers’ top demands(Source: “Driving Digital Transformation: New Skills For Leaders, New Role For The CIO” Harvard Business Review, 2015)40%40% of today’s top incumbents in each industry are expected to be displaced by digital disruption in the next  ve years.(Source: “Digital Vortex: How Digital Disruption Is Rede ning Industries”, The Global Center for Digital Business Transformation, June, 2015)17]]></page><page Index="18" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[TECHNOLOGY VISIONBrochure Design   DIGITAL WORKPLACE18]]></page><page Index="19" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[  Brochure DesignTHE RISE OF THE DIGITAL CITIZEN TRANSFORMS THE WAY WE WORKThe linesare blurring.The lines between work and home, as mobile devices allow us to take our work with us and our personal cloud to work.The lines between how we access information as con- sumers and how we want to access information as em- ployees or entrepreneurs.The lines between our physi- cal office and our digital one, as teams assemble and dis- semble in a variety of ways, sometimes never meeting face to face.Employees, accustomed to being an empowered consumer, are seeking that same empowerment at work. As a result, they are bringing technology prevalent in their lives outside of work into their offices, whether physical or virtual. They demand rapid access to knowledge and experts to make data-driven decisions in real time.Meanwhile, partners are demanding more and more self-service options for interaction. Customers are be- coming ever more vocal and impatient in their experiences with businesses. Employees are left scrambling for real-time, effective ways to serve up stellar service.Enter the digital workplace, an intelligent computing environment that promotes employee, customer, and partner engagement and effectiveness. From the enterprise social network to smart decision support, virtual personal assistants to salesforce automation, new digital ways of working are upon us.In an interesting twist, these tech-fueled ways of working are not in most cases being driven by IT departments, but rather by lines of business that have taken matters into their own hands.As part of the rise of the citizen integrator, employee teams are identifying, sourcing, and deploying their own solutions to support changing needs, increasingly turning to self-service options in the cloud. As digital work- place technologies become democratized, the revolution will amp up in earnest, as digital and mission-critical work become inextricably intertwined.1970%“By 2021, more than 70% of business users will be substantially provisioned with cloud office capabilities.”(Source: “Predicts 2017: Boosting Business Results Through Personal Choice in the Digital Workplace” Gartner, 2017)]]></page><page Index="20" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[TECHNOLOGY VISIONBrochure Design   DIGITAL DEXTERITY AT ALL LEVELS OF THE ORGANIZATIONAgile organizational models have replaced the hierarchies of old, bringing with them a  uidity in where and how decisions are made. Increasingly aided by machine intelligence, decisions are made closer to the point of action and impact. Tools that promote breaking down organizational idea siloes—from crowd-sourcing support to pro- cess hacking—will continue to develop and be adopted at a rapid pace.An influx of emerging technologies from the con- sumer space will continue for the foreseeable future, generally brought in by individual groups rather than in lockstep, centralized fashion. IT departments will struggle to absorb these new technologies and capabilities, while trying des- perately to connect technology to important business outcomes in a cohesive secure fashion.The savvy will develop a flexible roadmap for their digital workplace, which allows for the in- flux of new technologies and capabilities but provides a framework to incorporate these into the enterprise nervous system. It is only through such a roadmap that teams can unlock and ac- celerate the true value of digital.The era of the autonomous, empowered employ- ee citizen is upon us. Leadership teams will need to exploit digital dexterity to boost performance, as well as promote creativity and innovation, in order to serve customers’ increasing demands.20]]></page><page Index="21" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[  Brochure DesignDIGITAL WORKPLACE CAPABILITIESDigital Workplace capabilities are generally grouped into three categories. They should be self-service, responsive, intelligent, ambient applications.KNOWLEDGE APPSCommunity of Practice Matter Management Experience DiscoveryPROCESS APPSNew Matter Intake New Business Intake Partner Lateral MovesCOLLABORATION APPSTeam Sites and Intranet Doc Assembly2/3 of senior management across EMEA believe that optimizing the cloud, applications and mobile devices is a strategic priority. But, half of all organizations have no foreseeable plans to implement a digital work- place strategy.(Source: “Aruba Study: Two Thirds of SMEs in EMEA are Set for the Digital Workplace, But Company Strategy is Struggling to Keep Up,” CMX World, September 26, 2016)EMPOWERMENT COMES WITH BLURRED LINESAs the digital workplace takes shape, the future is bright. Assistance from machines who can take mundane work off of the back of human employ- ees should be a positive change. Humans will be freed up to take on greater innovation and crea- tivity, while shedding the mundane.Empowered employees will have the information they need, when they need it. They will leverage modern tools to find solutions that work and im- plement them rapidly, better serving customers and meeting myriad deadlines.We have really only just begun to tap the service of human potential in the workplace.Taken a step further, we see virtual and aug- mented reality immersing employees for train- ing, instruction and personal collaboration.21]]></page><page Index="22" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[TECHNOLOGY VISIONBrochure Design   REIMAGINING THE WORKPLACE: PEOPLE ENABLED BY TECHNOLOGYThe future hybrid workforce (part machine, part human) brings with it a change in roles. Routine work will be automated without necessity for hu- man intervention. Humans will be freed up to do what they do best - non-routine, creative, inno- vative work. Real-time analytics, contextualized context and machine learning will support them in this role.The new digital workplace contains a plethora of employee and corporate-sanctioned devices. SaaS, app-fueled, technology in the workplace is now about how to further engage employees and advance the business. The challenge will be to take these individual apps and make them an ecosystem of tools, smart tools that work across siloes and information stores, to fuel new in- sights and ways of doing things.Virtual personal assistants will provide teams greater effortless access to ambient knowledge. Curated collections of personalized, context-rich information will be the new norm. In the fore- seeable future, voice-driven computer interac- tions with devices like Amazon Echo, Apple’s Siri or Microsoft’s Cortana will be deeply embedded into how we do business, tapping into ambient knowledge to answer questions we have not even posed yet.Taken a step further, we see virtual and aug- mented reality immersing employees for train- ing, instruction and personal collaboration.22]]></page><page Index="23" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[  Brochure Design“Employees should be able to access information based on its relevancy to the goal at hand, versus information by silo or location. Intelligent agents need to be context specific and location agnostic.”—Ken Kuzdas, Director of Technology, Digital Workplace, NeudesicTHE EVOLUTION OF VIRTUAL PERSONAL ASSISTANTSAccording to Gartner, by 2020, four out of 10 high performers will distribute their work across a team of “virtual doppelgangers” to boost personal productivity. This process will be enabled by the rapid evolu- tion of VPAs over the next several years.HEAR MEVPAs can respond to queries and requests. “Pull up the quarterly results spreadsheet.”KNOW MEVPAs understand personal needs and proactively take action. Knowing Monday’s schedule is back-to-back meetings with no time for lunch, VPA orders from your favorite takeout restaurant and has delivered to office.SEE MEVPAs understand the context of the individual, whether at home, work or in car, or on a particular device.BE MEConflicting meetings are no longer an issue. Your VPA can “attend”a meeting virtually in your stead, taking notes and/or preparing a presentation.(Source: Matthew W. Cain, Stephen Kleynhans. “Empower Employees by Tapping Into the Top Emerging Trends in Digital Workplace Technologies” Gartner, July 14, 2016) 23]]></page><page Index="24" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[TECHNOLOGY VISIONBrochure Design   PREDICTIVE ENTERPRISE24]]></page><page Index="25" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[  Brochure DesignTHE CRYSTAL BALL EFFECT: ADVANCED ANALYTICS HITS THE ENTERPRISE WHITE SPACEAnalytics now sit squarely at the center of corporate strategy. Traditionally playing only a supporting role in executive decision- making, analyticsare now used as the basis for strategy optimization by leading companies.One major driver is a change in the business landscape, which now must support a service-based outcome economy. It is no longer enough to just meet customer de- sires, now companies must antici- pate them—and many serve those desires through platform-based ecosystems.Via just such an ecosystem, Am- azon uses analytics to recom- mend books based on a buyer’s previous likes, past purchases, shopping cart contents and what similar customers have bought. Amazon calls this “item-to-item collaborative filtering,” an algo- rithm that tailors browsing for re- turning customers.In similar fashion, Netflix brings new viewing options to subscribers based on their weekend binge watching and other browsing data. The company runs the information collected through a complex algorithm to best predict future favorites.Data has become the fuel for innovation in a digital economy that demands the new, the unanticipated, the customized.The barrage of insights that businesses want to glean from Big Data, housed within the seeming limitless stores of cloud computing, has in turn fueled advances in analytics platforms. These platforms have already changed the face of many industries drastically, with large revenue spikes in data-heavy industries such as insurance, healthcare and retail. Advanced analytics has become a competitive tool embedded into the busi- ness of business.25“Over the next few years, leading organizations will link analytic initiatives firmly to financial objectives, increase investments in advanced analytics, evolve comprehensive analytics centers of excellence, and incorporate a wider range of exogenous data.”(Source: “Predicts 2016: Analytics Strategy” Gartner, December 11, 2015)]]></page><page Index="26" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[TECHNOLOGY VISIONBrochure Design   “By 2018, decision optimization will no longer be a nichediscipline; it will become a best practice in leading organizations...”– Gartner Predicts 2016: Advanced Analytics Are at the Beating Heart of Algorithmic BusinessIOT AND VIRTUAL REALITYWith 25 billion connected devices expected by 2020, the amount of data generated by then is expected to total 44 zettabytes, 10% of it from the IoT alone . The amount of data to parse, as well as the number of potential options for ac- tion based on that data, will multiply exponen- tially. Whether executive teams are facing strate- gic, tactical or operational decisions, prescriptive analytics will suggest the optimal way to handle a situation—real or imagined—via virtual reality modeling.For instance, Los Angeles-based WASH Multi- family Laundry Systems (WASH) believes it is a technology company that just happens to do laundry. WASH is responsible for the upkeep of washers and dryers in 75,000 locations through- out the United States and Canada. Five million people do their laundry every week in a WASH laundry room.The company now runs Microsoft Dynamics as part of its technology platform. “It’s not a scav- enger hunt for data anymore. We can quickly get a report card based on machine inventory and open installation work orders,” according to Tommy Gates, VP of Operations.Now, using scanners, barcodes, smartphones and other devices, WASH employees can access the real-time data record on any one of the com- pany’s 500,000 machines. Using Power BI for Of- fice 365, WASH can also analyze the reliability of certain brands and models through tracking its service history.26]]></page><page Index="27" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[  Brochure DesignARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCEPrescriptive analytics is species-agnostic. In oth- er words, suggested actions can be fed to a hu- man (decision support) or to a system (decision automation). Or both. In the case of Stitch Fix, a machine-based algorithm combines with hu- man judgment for a curated customer collection meant to delight.As machines are trusted more and more to run an algorithm and make a decision without hu- man intervention, the issue of digital ethics and digital trust will come to the fore.How do we program self-learning machines to make unbiased decisions? In the case of a self-driving car, who does the car choose to hit when it recognizes an accident is unavoidable? The minivan with four children on board? The single pedestrian in the crosswalk? As compa- nies design and utilize AI-based products and services, decisions based on predictive modeling will become more complex.CHARACTERISTICS OF A PREDICTIVE ENTERPRISEDEMOCRATIZED DATA SCIENCE REIGNSIT-led enterprise reporting/BI gives way to business-led self-service analytics.A CONSTANT FLOW OF INFORMATION OCCURS THROUGHOUT THE ECOSYSTEMThese streams of external and internal data drive decisions.THE REARVIEW MIRROR DISAPPEARSAnalytics move from historical to real time and predictive.MACHINES GO FAR BEYOND ROTE ANALYTICSMachine learning brings deep intelligence throughout the business.27]]></page><page Index="28" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[TECHNOLOGY VISIONBrochure Design   ANALYTICS EVOLUTION29,500Number of hits on Glassdoor when searching for “data scientist.” The job title is listed as the number-one job in the United States, with a base salary of nearly $117,000.(Source: “Data Science Education Evolves to Meet Surging Demand”, Datanami, September 26, 2016)DESCRIPTIVE:Analyzing annual sales by region, segmentation of customers by revenue generatedPREDICTIVE:Sales forecasting, fraud detectionDIAGNOSTIC:Social media campaign success analysis, churn analysis on lost customersPRESCRIPTIVE:Price optimization, Marketing mix optimization28]]></page><page Index="29" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[  Brochure DesignEUREKA. DATA IN / INTELLIGENCE OUTData alone, however, is worthless. Raw data needs to be honed and polished into usable in- telligence. Whether mapping customer journeys or plotting a new manufacturing footprint, “data in / intelligence out” is the new mantra. To mine that intelligence, companies must use not indi- vidual data points but rather, data patterns. And Big Data is only as good as its rate of analysis. Speed matters. Because the company that pars- es the data in the most efficient, speedy way gets to innovation faster.Innovation centers on being able to predict what customers want before they even know it. To predict and then prescribe a “best choice” for market demand that may not even exist yet is becoming a science, thanks to analytics.Enter the algorithm economy. Algorithms are re- usable groupings of data-based code taking off in software development circles. Put data into an algorithm and, ideally, insight will come out the other end of that algorithm. And, the algorithm will self-learn the more it is applied. The possi- bilities for insight-as-a-service, when algorithm marketplaces combine with PaaS, continue to grow for businesses of all sizes. Evidence-based decision making is fast becoming a core compo- nent of the digital workplace.THE RX FOR DIGITAL LEADERSBecause analytics is no longer viewed via a rear- view, “where have we been” mirror, analyzing data has become more complex. Currently, ana- lytics is real-time and already future-focused at a select few leading organizations. Combining pre- dictive modeling, business rules and scoring— among other technologies—advanced analytics is changing the face of decision management.Over the next few years, we see prescriptive an- alytics as an area for investment by many enter- prises, particularly because of its potential when combined with other technologies. Internally and externally, companies will capitalize on IoT sensor data and artificial intelligence not only to help them better tailor customer offers, but also to do things like reduce factory downtime and improve shipping times.From retailers customizing services for shoppers, to governments plotting the best emergency re- sponse, prescriptive analytics will contribute to an explosion of decision optimization scenari- os—changing the face of entire industries.COMBINING HUMAN AND MACHINE INTELLIGENCE FOR BETTER PREDICTIONSSan Francisco-based Stitch Fix styles clients by anticipating what would fit well with their current ward- robe and style, based on Pinterest profiles and other social data. Self-learning algorithms produce recommendations for stylists who use their personal experience and knowledge of the customer to curate those recommendations down to just five items. As customers purchase, answer questions and/or communicate with their stylist, each “fix” (wardrobe items sent regularly for potential purchase) becomes increasingly accurate.29]]></page><page Index="30" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[TECHNOLOGY VISIONBrochure Design   “Neudesic’s Advanced Predictive Visualization and Cloud Bursting Solution gives us a strong foundation for using predictive analysis to increase the accuracy of our demand forecasting. Their implementation of Azure ML accelerates the iterative process, allowing us to arrive at our most accurate model sooner. We also now have the tools and roadmap to deploy an effective internal data science team.”– Jason Wilhite, Manager, Business Intelligence Services, SRPREAL-TIME, AFFORDABLE ANALYTICSAT SCALE CHANGES THE GAMELower memory and storage costs, courtesy of the cloud and in-mem- ory technologies, are now du jour. Because of these shifts, architec- tures are now in play. Companies are moving from the old-style, cen- tralized data warehouse to virtual warehouses in the cloud.In-memory computing allows companies to apply analytics to large stores of data at one time. And with the normalization of universal, non-volatile memory, data scientists will be able to analyze volumes that dwarf today’s in-memory databases.Today, businesses of all sizes can access insights as a service thanks to cloud-based analytic tools such as Microsoft’s Analytics Platform Sys- tem (APS). The race is on to see which competitors in which industries will create or buy the best algorithms, mine the best data insights and translate all of the above into something customers have never seen before—but fast realize they cannot live without.A SYSTEM THAT THINKS LIKE ITS HUMAN CREATORSThe Salt River Project (SRP), one of the largest public power utilities in the United States, pro- vides electricity and water to more than two mil- lion people in Central Arizona.After installing smart meters, the utility was del- uged with data—more than 100 million rows per day. Neudesic implemented a predictive analyt- ics solution at the utility to accurately predict fu- ture energy demand.This solution along with the predictive analytics roadmap, allows SRP executives to strategical- ly and incrementally invest at each stage of the solution development process.Having the right demand forecast allows SRP to produce the right amount of power as well as balance the power grid to minimize outages and overloads.30]]></page><page Index="31" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[  Brochure DesignTECHNOLOGY VISION AUTHORSTIM MARSHALL - Chief Technology O cer, FounderA LITTLE BIT ABOUT TIMAs the leader of the technology team, Tim is responsible for de ning the technological trail Neudesic blazes to em- power organizations in understanding and leveraging business solutions using the Microsoft Technology Platform.Tim’s wealth of experience in di erent technologies, along with his extensive expertise across a wide breadth of vertical markets, enables him to assist organizations in making proper technical decisions that help them achieve their visions. His involvement with the technical aspect of the business is deep, as evidenced through his expert presentations at major industry events and his work with development teams nationally.JASON NOBLE - Vice President - Digital Innovation GroupA LITTLE BIT ABOUT JASONAs Vice President of the Digital Innovation Group, Jason drives the daily innovation pipeline that fuels Neudesic’s cli- ent solutions and successes. He owns a team of technology experts, dedicated to digital enterprise transformation through trending technologies including collaboration, integration, cloud, data and analytics.Jason has spent over twenty years helping medium-sized businesses and Fortune 500 enterprises build and manage complex, mission critical digital platforms that advance collaboration through knowledge and management applica- tions. In addition to his Vice President role, Jason also leads product development for Neudesic’s Firm Directory and Pulse products.TECHNOLOGY VISION CONTRIBUTORSBRENDON BIRDOES - Vice President - Digital Innovation GroupA LITTLE BIT ABOUT BRENDONBrendon is a technology professional with over 15 years experience helping clients with technology strategy, architec- ture and implementation of technology solutions. His passion is utilizing existing and emerging technologies especially in Cloud and Mobility, along with proven delivery practices to achieve Digital Transformation. Brendon is currently a Vice President of the Digital Innovation Group at Neudesic shaping technology vision & strategy focusing on innovative solutions for our clients.DAVID BARRETTDirector of Technology - Digital IntegrationCHAD THOMASDirector of Technology - Digital PlatformKEN KUZDASDirector of Technology - Digital WorkplaceORION GEBREMEDHINDirector of Technology - Predictive Enterprise31]]></page><page Index="32" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[vision.neudesic.comThe shift to digital business is a tectonic shift. As you look to digitally enable your organization, people, strategies, processes and technology models will need to be rethought and redesigned, for a new world. Simply adding a digital overlay to your business will not su ce.Those companies that maintain or gain a leadership position will be the ones that look, un inchingly, at what is required to reinvent themselves.Shaping a digital business is no small task, but the payo  is clear. Finding your organization’s sweet spot in this radical shift means claiming the pole position as the race to digital begins.SHAPING YOUR DIGITAL BUSINESS]]></page></pages></Search>